famousscientists.org 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

At _Famous Scientists_ , your privacy is our top priority. This page describes the types of personal information received and collected by _Famous Scientists_ and how we use it.

### Personal Information

_Famous Scientists_ does not need any information which can be traced back to, and identify a unique user. Certain features of the website, for instance comments, do require a valid email address to verify legitimate users. We guarantee that the information provided to us would never be shared with third-parties.

### Log Files

Like many other websites, _Famous Scientists_ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the website, track user’s movement around the website, and gather demographic information. None the data recorded is linked to information that could personally identify a unique individual.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

Third party service providers may store information as cookies on your computer. Refer to the following sections to understand what information is collected and how to opt out of the process.

### DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on _Famous Scientists_. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to websites. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at this URL (https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

### Advertisers

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks, like Google Adsense, may use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on _Famous Scientists_ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

_Famous Scientists_ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### Copyrights

_Famous Scientists_ ensures that there are no copyright infringements on our website. If you find anything that could be considered a violation of the copyright norms, please [contact us](https://www.famousscientists.org/contact) immediately.
